[Applause]
[Vỗ tay]
[Music]
[âm nhạc]
We are grateful to our compassionate mother, the teacher who taught us the true
há về cô người mẹ Hiên từ Thầy cho con
nature of things. This is evil, so we must abandon it; this is meditation. We must strive to cultivate it. We are grateful to our teacher, Cao Ca, with boundless love and wisdom, who listens to all our
thương trí tuệ bao la đang nghe hết
suffering and shows us a way
những lời đau khổ chỉ cho con một lối đi
out.
ra
[Music] We are
[âm nhạc]
grateful to our teacher, we are grateful to her. We vow to guide
biết ơn cô chúng con biết ơn cô Nguyền
us,
hướng con ngay trangc ngồ không ngày khó
day and night, diligently leading us through the
khô ngày đêm tinh tấn dìu dắp chúng con
garden of delusion. We are grateful
vườn biế
to our compassionate mother, the teacher who taught us the true
mê há về cô người mẹ Hiên từ dậy cho con
nature of things. This is evil, so we must abandon it;
pháp phận chân như đây là ác con đên từ
this is meditation. We must strive to cultivate it.
bò đây là thiền con phải gắng
Cao Ca, the teacher, with
tu ri Sơn cô người thầy Cao cà một tình
boundless love and wisdom, listens to all our
thương trí tuệ bao la lắng nghe hết
suffering and shows us a way out.
những lời đau khổ chỉ cho con một lối đi
We vow to
ra hành ngyên bồ đê chúng con khắc Nghi
always strive diligently, practicing harmoniously, bringing the Buddha
luôn tình tấn thức hành hòa hợp đưa Phật
Dharma to the world. We repay her kindness and fulfill her wishes.
Pháp đang Dận ra thế giới đèn đáp Ân cô
[Music] We are grateful
[âm nhạc]
to our compassionate mother, the teacher who taught us the true
l h về cô người mẹ Hiên từ dạy cho con
nature of things. This is evil, so we must abandon it;
pháp Phần chân như đây là ác con nên từ
this is meditation. We must strive to cultivate it. We are grateful to our teacher, Cao
bò đây là thiền con phải gắng
Ca, with boundless
t biết ơn cô người thấy cao cà một tình
love and wisdom, who listens to all our suffering and practices.  These
thương chí tuệ bao la lắng nghe hết
words of suffering only show me a path to
những lời đau khổ chỉ cho con một lối đi
enlightenment. We still engrave the meaning in our hearts. The Tan family practices
ra thành Nguyện Bồ Đề chúng còn khắc
harmony and
Nghi luôn Đình Tấn thức hành hòa hồng
brings the Buddha's teachings to the world, repaying the
đưa Phật pháp n dọn ra thế giới đèn đáp
kindness of the aunt.
Ân cô th tâm
Bringing the Buddha's teachings to the world, repaying the
l đưa Phật Pháp là dộng ra thế giới đền
kindness of the
đám ơn cô
aunt.
quả tấm
[Music]
[âm nhạc]
La I
la I